Clark W. Thompson papers, Inclusive: 1931-1966, undated, Bulk: 1959-1966
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Personal, 1933-1965, undated; 6
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence (5 of 5) (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence with Colorado County (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence with Galveston County (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence with Goliad County (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence with Matagorda County (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence with Wharton County (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - 1952 Campaign, Data and Expenses (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - 1952 Campaign, Election (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - 1952 Campaign, Invitations (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - 1952 Campaign, News (1 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - 1952 Campaign, News (2 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - 1952 Campaign, Organization Meeting (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - 1952 Campaign, Primary Results (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - 1952 Campaign, Radio Scripts (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - 1952 Campaign, Thank-You Letters (1 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - 1952 Campaign, Thank-You Letters (2 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - 1954 Campaign, Congratulations for Successful Camp Letters (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - 1954 Campaign, Correspondence (1 of 7) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - 1954 Campaign, Correspondence (2 of 7) (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - 1954 Campaign, Correspondence (3 of 7) (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - 1954 Campaign, Correspondence (4 of 7) (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 1954 Campaign, Correspondence (5 of 7) (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - 1954 Campaign, Correspondence (6 of 7) (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - 1954 Campaign, Correspondence (7 of 7) (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - 1954 Campaign, Correspondence with Lloyd Gregory (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - 1954 Campaign, Data and Expenses (1 of 3) (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - 1954 Campaign, Data and Expenses (2 of 3) (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - 1954 Campaign, Data and Expenses (3 of 3) (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - 1954 Campaign, Election Returns (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - 1954 Campaign, Invitations (1 of 3) (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - 1954 Campaign, Invitations (2 of 3) (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - 1954 Campaign, Invitations (3 of 3) (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - 1954 Campaign, Newspaper Clippings and Advertisements, 1954-1955 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - 1954 Campaign, Political Information, 9th District, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - 1954 Campaign, Radio and Television Schedules and Scripts (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - 1956 Campaign, Announcements (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Austin County (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Brazoria County (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Calhoun County (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Colorado County (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Fayette County (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Fort Bend County (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Galveston County (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Goliad County (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Jackson County (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Lavata County (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Matagorda County (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Victoria County (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Waller County (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - 1956 Campaign, Correspondence with Wharton County (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - 1956 Campaign, Data and Expenses (1 of 3) (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - 1956 Campaign, Data and Expenses (2 of 3) (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - 1956 Campaign, Data and Expenses (3 of 3) (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - 1956 Campaign, General Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - 1956 Campaign, Newspaper Clippings (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - 1956 Campaign, Political Materials (1 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - 1956 Campaign, Political Materials (2 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - 1958 Campaign, Announcements (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - 1958 Campaign, Correspondence with Austin, Brazos, and Calhoun Counties (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - 1958 Campaign, Correspondence with Chambers, Colorado, and Fayette Counties (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - 1958 Campaign, Correspondence with Fort Bend, Galveston, and Goliad Counties (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - 1958 Campaign, Correspondence with Jackson, Lavaca, and Matagorda Counties (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - 1958 Campaign, Correspondence with Victoria, Waller, and Wharton Counties (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - 1958 Campaign, Data and Expenses (1 of 3) (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - 1958 Campaign, Data and Expenses (2 of 3) (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - 1958 Campaign, Data and Expenses (3 of 3) (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - 1958 Campaign, Loyalty Affidavits and Ballot (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - 1958 Campaign, Newspaper Clippings (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - 1960 Campaign, Announcements (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - 1960 Campaign, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - 1960 Campaign, Data and Expenses (1 of 2) (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - 1960 Campaign, Data and Expenses (2 of 2) (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - 1960 Campaign, Loyalty Affidavits and Ballot (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - 1960 Campaign, Newspaper Clippings (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - 1961 Inauguration (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - 1962 Campaign, Ballot Applications (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - 1962 Campaign, Congratulatory Letters (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Austin County (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Brazoria County (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Calhoun County (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Chambers County (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Colorado County (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Fayette County (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Fort Bend County (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Galveston County (1 of 2) (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Galveston County (2 of 2) (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Goliad County (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Gregory, Lloyd (1 of 2), 1962-1965 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Gregory, Lloyd (2 of 2), 1962-1965 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Jackson County (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Jackson, Guy C., 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Lavaca County (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Matagorda County (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Oakes, Dave, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Post Office (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Victoria County (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Waller County (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - 1962 Campaign, Correspondence with Wharton County (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - 1962 Campaign, Data and Expenses (1 of 2) (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - 1962 Campaign, Data and Expenses (2 of 2) (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - 1962 Campaign, General Correspondence (1 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - 1962 Campaign, General Correspondence (2 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - 1962 Campaign, General Correspondence (3 of 3) (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - 1962 Campaign, Newspaper Clippings and Advertisements (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - 1962 Campaign, Radio Scripts and Press Releases (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 1962 Campaign, Thank-You Letters (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - 1964 Campaign, Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 1964 Campaign, Data and Expenses (1 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 1964 Campaign, Data and Expenses (2 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - 1964 Campaign, Correspondence and Speeches (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - 1965 Inauguration Invitation, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - 87th Congress, 2nd Session Attendance Materials, 1962-1963 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Advertisements and Prints, 1952-1954 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Democratic National Committee and Politics (1 of 2), 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Democratic National Committee and Politics (1 of 2), 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Democratic National Committee and National Politics (1 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Democratic National Committee and National Politics (2 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Democratic National Committee and National Politics (3 of 3), 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Local Politics, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Local Politics, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Local Politics (1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Local Politics (2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Names to Remember (1 of 2), 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Names to Remember (2 of 2), 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - National Politics, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - National Politics, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - National Politics, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - National Politics, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - National Politics (1 of 3), 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - National Politics (2 of 3), 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - National Politics (3 of 3), 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1952-1964 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Texas Apportionment, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Texas Delegation, 1959-1962 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Texas Politics, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Texas Politics (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Texas Politics (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Texas Senate Resolution, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Public, 1946-1966, undated; 7
  This short series focuses on Thompson's communications with the executive branch, other congressional districts, and the media. There are several folders of communications concerning fellow Texan and President Lyndon B. Johnson as well as visits by Thompson and his constituents to the White House. Additionally, there is a copy of the Voting Rights speech delivered by President Johnson to Congress - a measure that Thompson firmly opposed.
  There is also a short section of folders dealing with national and international correspondence. These materials focus on the issues of immigration from 1947 to 1963, as well as foreign affairs and communications from outside of Thompson’s district.
  Thompson’s mode of communication to his district developed and changed over time. The introduction of television is showcased in this series with invoices and scripts from Thompson’s appearances on screen (1961-1966). His use of the radio, however, goes back much earlier as his radio scripts demonstrate. As early as 1946, Thompson was actively using this medium to reach his constituents. Overall, the series is arranged topically, then alphabetically, and is in good condition.
  - Presidential Speech to Congress, Voting Rights Legislation, 1965 March (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - White House, 1963-1964 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - White House, 1965-1966 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Citizenship, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Common Market, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Cuba (1 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Cuba (2 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Cuba (3 of 3), 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - District of Columbia, 1965-1966 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Immigration, 1947-1948 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Immigration (1 of 2), 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Immigration (2 of 2), 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Immigration, 1951-1953 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Immigration, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Immigration, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Immigration, 1960-1963 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Latin America, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Mexico, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Projects Outside 9th District, 1957-1961 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Samoan Airlines, Larry Coleman, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Sam Rayburn Foundation, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Selective Service, 1965-1966 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Soil and Water Conservation, 1960-1966 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Veterans Affairs Center, Myron Cowen, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - World Bank, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Television, General, Invoices, 1958-1961 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Television, General, Invoices, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Television, General, Invoices, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Television, General, Invoices, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Television, General, Invoices, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - KHOU, Television Broadcast Service Highlights, 1961 May (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Television Scripts, 1961-1963 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Television Scripts, 1963-1966 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Radio Recorder Data, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Radio Scripts, 1946 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Radio Scripts, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Radio Scripts (1 of 2), 1948 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Radio Scripts (2 of 2), 1948 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Radio Scripts, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Radio Scripts, 1961 January-February (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Radio Scripts, 1961 March-May (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Radio Scripts, 1961 June-July (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Radio Scripts, 1961 August-December (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Radio Scripts, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Radio Scripts, 1963 January-March (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Radio Scripts, 1963 April-May (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Radio Scripts, 1963 June-July (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Radio Scripts, 1963 August-September (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Radio Scripts, 1963 October-December (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Radio Scripts, 1964 January-April (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Radio Scripts, 1964 May-June (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Radio Scripts, 1965 February-March (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Radio Scripts, 1965 April-September (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Radio Scripts, 1966 March-April (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Radio Scripts, 1966 May (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Radio Station Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Radio Station Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Scrapbooks, 1946-1964; 8
  This series is comprised of eight scrapbooks dated 1946-1964. The scrapbooks house clippings, photographs, and other memorabilia from Clark Thompson’s tenure in Congress. There is some significant overlap in the chronologies of the individual scrapbooks. Overall, the series is in good condition.
  - Scrapbook, 1946-1947 (Box 97 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1947 (Box 98 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1947-1951 (Box 99 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1948-1955 (Box 100 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1955-1956 (Box 101 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1956-1958 (Box 102 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1958-1961 (Box 103 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1962-1964 (Box 104 OVZ, Folder 1)
- Texas Affairs, 1946-1966, undated; 9
  This extensive series contains a wide array of materials related to Thompson’s adoptive home state (Texas) and region (Galveston). There is a large selection of speeches and articles written by or about Thompson ranging from 1958 to 1966. These folders are followed by a voluminous collection of constituent correspondence. Arranged topically, this section highlights the range of requests and comments that Thompson received. The next segment of folders is arranged by the name of the city and county involved. These titles are further described with the topic of discussion. Because Thompson represented a coastal region, many of the issues he dealt with addressed the usage and construction of local harbors as well as the consolidation and creation of several military installations in the area.
  This series also contains materials pertaining to four major topics and events that impacted Thompson's district: Hurricane Carla, the Public Water and Resources Department, rivers and harbors, and the Texas City Disaster. It is worth noting that each of these topics deals in some way with Thompson’s district’s proximity to the Gulf of Mexico and the opportunities or problems that closeness caused. Documents relating to Hurricane Carla chronicle Thompson’s response to the damage caused by the storm’s landfall in 1961. The southern part of his district had been particularly affected. The Public Water and Resources Department folders focus on the actions of the boards responsible for each of Texas’s prominent river basins that flow into the Gulf of Mexico. Materials about rivers and harbors are alphabetically arranged by topic and contain information on navigation and improvement projects from 1947 to 1962. Lastly, the Texas City Disaster folders contain correspondence, litigation, and legislation in the wake of the 1947 harbor explosion that claimed 581 lives from Thompson’s district. Overall, the series is arranged topically, then alphabetically, and is in good condition.
  - Clippings and Newspaper Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Speeches and Articles, 1958-1959 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Speeches and Articles, 1960-1962 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Texas Newsprint Company, General, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Texas Newsprint Company, Mill Construction, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Texas Newsprint Company, General, 1964-1965 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Academy Appointments, 1949-1951 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Academy Appointments, 1953-1957 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Ben Cannan, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Congratulations, 1963-1965 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Employment Assistance, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Employment Assistance, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Employment Assistance, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Employment Assistance, 1965 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Employment Assistance, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Flag Requests, 1959-1962 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Flag Requests, 1963-1966 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Louisiana-Dallas Limited Stop Airplane Service, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Patronage, 1959-1964 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Summer Employment, National Park Service, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Summer Employment, D.C. Office, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Valedictorians and Salutatorians, 1965-1966 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Visitors Expected in Texas, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Visitors Expected in D.C., 1961 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Visitors Expected in D.C., 1962 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Visitors Expected in D.C., 1964 December-1965 May (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Visitors Expected in D.C., 1965 June-December (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Visitors Expected in D.C., 1966 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Hurricane Carla, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Information Requests, General, 1959-1960 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Information Requests, General (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Information Requests, General (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Information Requests, General, 1962 January-August (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Information Requests, General, 1962 September-December (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Information Requests, General, 1964 July-December (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Information Requests, General, 1965 January-March (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Information Requests, General, 1965 April-August (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Information Requests, General, 1965 September-December (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Information Requests, General, 1966 January-April (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Information Requests, General, 1966 May-September (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Information Requests, General, 1966 September-December (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Information Requests, 9th District, 1960-1966 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Information Requests, Agriculture, 1960-1962 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Information Requests, Agriculture, 1965-1966 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Information Requests, Agriculture Yearbooks (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Information Requests, Agriculture Yearbooks (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Information Requests, Agriculture Yearbook (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Information Requests, Agriculture Yearbook (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Information Requests, Agriculture Yearbook (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Information Requests, Agriculture Yearbook, 1966 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Information Requests, Capital Punishment, 1961-1965 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Information Requests, Census Bureau, 1960-1964 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Information Requests, Civil Rights, 1964-1966 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Information Requests, Communism, 1961-1962 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Information Requests, Congressional Directory, 1960-1963 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Information Requests, "Congressional Record", 1961-1964 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Information Requests, Education and Schools, 1960-1966 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Information Requests, Employment, 1961-1966 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Information Requests, Federal Aid to Education, 1961-1965 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Information Requests, Federal Service Joint Crusade, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Information Requests, Firearms, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Information Requests, Former Presidents, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Information Requests, Gold Standard, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Information Requests, Homes for the Elderly, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Information Requests, House of Representatives, 1961-1966 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Information Requests, House Un-American Activities Committee, 1961-1966 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Information Requests, International Affairs, 1960-1966 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Information Requests, Lowering the Voting Age, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Information Requests, Military Affairs, 1960-1966 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Information Requests, Publication Requests (1 of 2), 1960-1966 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Information Requests, Publication Requests (2 of 2), 1960-1966 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Information Requests, Requests from Students, 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Information Requests, Requests from Students, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Information Requests, Requests from Students, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Information Requests, Requests from Students, 1965 January-March (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Information Requests, Requests from Students, 1965 April-October (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Information Requests, Requests from Students, 1965 November-December (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Information Requests, Requests from Students, 1966 January-February (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Information Requests, Requests from Students, 1966 March-November (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Information Requests, Small Businesses, 1961-1965 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Information Requests, Student Loans, 1961-1966 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Information Requests, Surplus Property, 1950-1962 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Information Requests, United Nations, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Alvin, First National Bank Charter, 1959 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Brazoria, Fair, 1959-1960 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Brownsville, Cold-Water Seafood Corporation, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Calhoun, Matagorda Island Right-of-Way (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Calhoun, Matagorda Island Right-of-Way (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Calhoun, Matagorda Water Range, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Freeport, Highway to Galveston, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Freeport, Saltwater Conversion Plant, 1960-1962 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Galveston, General Local Matters, 1955-1957 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Galveston, General Local Matters, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Galveston, General Local Matters, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Galveston, General Local Matters, 1963 January-July (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Galveston, General Local Matters, 1963 August-December (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Galveston, General Local Matters, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Galveston, General Local Matters, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Galveston, General Local Matters, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Galveston, Beach Erosion, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Galveston, Camp Hitchcock, 1959-1961 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Galveston, City Hall Project, 1964-1965 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Galveston, Ford Dealership, 1958-1961 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Galveston, Fort Crockett, 1959-1961 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Galveston, Galveston County Research Council, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 8)